<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <channel>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://www.90min.com/posts.rss"/>
    <title>All the latest breaking football news, transfer rumours, analysis, and match reports - 90min</title>
    <link>http://www.90min.com/</link>
    <description>All the latest football news from 90min including transfer, analysis, reports, predictions and more</description>
    <item>
      <title>Man Utd's Strongest XI Can Beat Anyone But the Need for Rotation Still Makes the Rest of the Season a Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/man-utd-s-strongest-xi-can-beat-anyone-but-the-need-for-rotation-still-makes-the-rest-of-the-season-a-challenge-01ec0bx0q4vw?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Jamie Spencer</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af2398f4ae5030f3d087742dde28062d</guid>
      <description>Manchester United are in a good place right now, arguably a better place than they have been in at any point since Sir Alex Ferguson retired. Saturday evening marked a 14th game without defeat as the team booked a place in the FA Cup semi-finals for only the third time since 2011. But this remains a work very much in progress and the positive steps made in recent months are still relatively early in the process. Ole Gunnar Solskjaer must choose his starting XI carefully United deserve credit...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Norwich-City-v-Manchester-United---FA-Cup-Quarter--9bb77538fb059029acc303b6f9417b82.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everton vs Leicester Preview: How to Watch on TV, Live Stream, Kick Off Time &amp; Team News</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/everton-vs-leicester-preview-how-to-watch-on-tv-live-stream-kick-off-time-team-news-01ebzzj9per3?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Duncan Mitchell</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9371bbb1c7fdf0f1cf0c4ab455060c42</guid>
      <description>News After a weekend of entertaining FA Cup action, the Premier League comes back to the fore this week. Leicester, who were dumped out the cup by Chelsea at the weekend, travel to Goodison Park to face an Everton side fresh off their first win since the restart. The Toffees, who sit 12th in the table, have looked far stronger defensively since the return, but have looked less than clinical in front of goal as their Europa League push splutters. Leicester have similar problems but with...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Norwich-City-v-Everton-FC---Premier-League-8e7ced2d124feb58752b5098595e6763.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of the Attacking Midfield Role</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/the-evolution-of-the-attacking-midfield-role-01eby8xs814h?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Robbie Copeland</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a65d69f6eba671f27ca9ab4fe9a2717</guid>
      <description>Vague, grey and undefinable, no position in the history of football has gone through as many identity shifts as the enigmatic No.10. It's a tactical anomaly, a liquid role in a sport historically rooted in tactical structure, changing its form like a chameleon depending on the needs of the game at the time. Compare Johan Cruyff or Diego Maradona with Steven Gerrard or Frank Lampard and you'll find few similarities, except that, at one point, all have defined what it means to be an attacking...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Dutch-Eredivisie---FC-Den-Haag-v-Ajax-8e1dba8586f114071a6bc834acab8240.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What We Learned from the FA Cup Quarter Finals</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/what-we-learned-from-the-fa-cup-quarter-finals-01ebv767qr23?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Ali Rampling</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">040074ef143f3d9932412253dd53a5be</guid>
      <description>The FA Cup quarter finals took place over the weekend, with Manchester United, Arsenal, Chelsea and Manchester City booking their place in the last four at the expense of Norwich, Sheffield United Leicester and Newcastle. It was victory all round for the visitors as United recorded a 2-1 victory at Norwich and Arsenal beat Sheffield United by the same scoreline, while Chelsea won 1-0 at Leicester and City secured a 2-0 win over Newcastle. So what did we learn from the FA Cup quarter finals?...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Norwich-City-v-Manchester-United---FA-Cup-Quarter--16616b8d748d2136a5e15e939c4448a7.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlético Madrid Might Have a Striker Problem, But it's Nothing Compared to Barcelona's</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/atletico-madrid-might-have-a-striker-problem-but-it-s-nothing-compared-to-barcelona-s-01ebzvt6zbtd?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Declan Houten</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d636abfd7a0c2fa156bbcd11056bb7a3</guid>
      <description>In football there are two main reasons why transfer policy goes badly. The first involves knowing what you want, but not having the means to get it, and often settling for less. This is a pretty simple dilemma that all but about seven of Europe's top teams will be familiar with - a case in point would be Spurs wanting Sergio Agüero in 2012, but through lack of means ending up with a 32-year-old Louis Saha. Ok, that was a rather extreme example. Most clubs have certain constraints to work...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Celta-de-Vigo-v-FC-Barcelona---La-Liga-Santander-d07f9f49c35c6bc51f9c104767c8b872.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90min's Definitive European Power Rankings: Week 27 - Grace &amp; Frankie Special</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/90min-s-definitive-european-power-rankings-week-27-grace-frankie-special-01ebzk3rwked?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Jack Gallagher</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02ab27da2594f2e19dea284f78318abe</guid>
      <description>cial Following a week in which: - Liverpool WON their first league title in three decades. - Bayern Munich WON their first league title in 12 months. - Arsenal WON their first game of football in a lifetime. We, with a martini glass in one hand and an edible in the other, rank the current 15 best teams in Europe using quotes from Netflix OG classic 'Grace and Frankie'. 15. Borussia Dortmund (Down 9) BVB were thumped in their final game of the season "I played by all the rules! Why didn’t you...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Liverpool-FC-v-Crystal-Palace---Premier-League-19a6168598775def4f78be1df4058576.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheffield Utd Agree Loan Extension for Man Utd Goalkeeper Dean Henderson</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/sheffield-utd-agree-loan-extension-for-man-utd-goalkeeper-dean-henderson-01ec0am58pcw?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Jamie Spencer</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51b40f23fdeb8f5ccac7bf266b8a66ec</guid>
      <description>Sheffield United will keep goalkeeper Dean Henderson on loan for the remainder of the delayed 2019/20 after reaching an agreement with parent club Manchester United. Henderson’s initial loan at Bramall Lane was due to expire this week, which ordinarily would have been well after the end of the campaign. But the unique circumstances this season has thrown up ensured that a special temporary extension needed to be agreed. Henderson has enjoyed a strong season with Sheffield Utd There were no...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Aston-Villa-v-Sheffield-United---Premier-League-9308efc519294ce41655f8da9fabd5b2.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zinedine Zidane Reacts to Ridiculous Karim Benzema Backheel Assist</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/zinedine-zidane-reacts-to-ridiculous-karim-benzema-backheel-assist-01ebzm6jx08x?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Tom Gott</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7701a63dad18ff18e657e9bf085aab5</guid>
      <description>Who'd have thought that being out of Cristiano Ronaldo's shadow would be so fun? Real Madrid hitman Karim Benzema is loving every second of being his side's talisman, after taking some time to grow into it last season. He has already bagged 22 goals in all competitions and added his tenth assist of the season with a sumptuous backheel pass for Casemiro against Espanyol. Just a casual backheel assist from Benzema, no big deal! ? Casemiro finishes and Madrid lead just before half time ⚪...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Real-Sociedad-v-Real-Madrid-CF----La-Liga-1aa8544c39512e35b8c5d2d333db8316.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ole Gunnar Solskjaer Reveals Angel Gomes Is Set to Leave Man Utd on June 30</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/ole-gunnar-solskjaer-reveals-angel-gomes-is-set-to-leave-man-utd-on-june-30-01ebzqz2e2eg?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Jamie Spencer</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36cb88464fd0e81578d1251c3aa63022</guid>
      <description>Manchester United manager Ole Gunnar Solskjaer has revealed that academy graduate Angel Gomes, who made his first-team debut at the age of just 16 in May 2017, looks likely to leave the club when his contract expires this week. Gomes is out of contract on 30 June and the club have not managed to reach an agreement with the 19-year-old about extending his stay at Old Trafford. Gomes has played 10 first-team games in 3 years “Got no news, nothing, so doesn't look like [he will stay],” Solskjaer...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/Manchester-United-v-Norwich-City---Premier-League-d6d9d8696c391b96654c7dbccc1199f9.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gianluigi Buffon and Giorgio Chiellini Sign New Juventus Deals</title>
      <link>https://www.90min.com/posts/gianluigi-buffon-and-giorgio-chiellini-sign-new-juventus-deals-01ec065wymkb?utm_source=RSS</link>
      <author>Ali Rampling</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">053433da415c0f943d058460a7685b2d</guid>
      <description>Juventus have confirmed Gianluigi Buffon and Giorgio Chiellini have put pen to paper on new deals that will keep the pair at the club until 2021. Both Buffon and Chiellini's contracts were set to expire at the end of June 2020, but the veterans have extended their stay in Turin for a further year. 2️⃣0️⃣2️⃣1️⃣ | Una fantastica notizia: @gianluigibuffon &amp;amp; Giorgio @chiellini hanno rinnovato per un altro anno con la Juventus! ✍️❤️⚪⚫https://t.co/gxubRWKqaV pic.twitter.com/EgV25GfLrj —...</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://images2.minutemediacdn.com/image/upload/c_fill,w_912,h_516,f_auto,q_auto,g_auto/shape/cover/sport/AC-Milan-v-Juventus---Serie-A-7486d094bd4084d4b6474efcf7c50fec.jpg?main_image=true&amp;imageType=.jpg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>